Frank Juval Quinones

Entrepreneurial, creative professional full of moxie, with a penchant for knowledge, systems thinking, and servant leadership; with twenty-six years of experience in graphic design, brand development, web development, and animation. I've generated solutions for major corporations including Marriott, Universal, and NBC.

EXPERIENCE

My versatility, resourcefulness, and initiative has served my previous employers very well. I'm the person they come to when they need help figuring out a particular piece of software, or if they need a different perspective in finding a solution. ◆ I'm always a student. I never stop learning. It's how one prevents becoming a dinosaur. Continual learning is also a way to improve one's workflow. ◆ It's important to put in the effort to build and nurture relationships because you never know what kind of amazing things can come from it. ◆ I've lead major projects, built teams, and influenced senior leadership. Please allow me the opportunity to put my experience in serving your company.

CAREER HISTORY

Front End Developer/Digital Designer, Universal Parks & Resorts — 2013–2020 Web Designer, AffiliateManager.com — 2012-2013 Web Designer, Marriott Vacation Club — 2011–2012 Sr. Graphic Designer, Digital Daydream — 2009–2010 Publications Artist, VisitOrlando — 2004–2008 Graphic Designer, Tupperware — 2002–2004 Graphic Artist, Ames True Temper — 2002 Graphic Artist/animator, Various Employers — 1994–2002

EDUCATION

Santa Fe College, Gainesville, Florida — A.A.S. in Graphic Design, 2001 University of Central Florida, Orlando Florida — Traditional Animation Program, 1997-1998 New World School of the Arts, Miami, Florida — Fine Arts Program, 1994-1996 Miami-Dade College — General Education, 1991-1993

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud: I began with Adobe 28 years ago with the very first Photoshop and Illustrator. I've grown with them since the beginning, to the Creative Suit, and Creative Cloud.

Code: HTML, CSS, JS, Git/Github, jQuery, GreenSock JS, CLI, Grunt, Gulp, Rest API, Sass, MarkDown, and more.

Tools: InVision/InVision Studio, Sketch, Slack, WordPress & other CMS, Figma, Abstract, After Effects, and more.

Other: Microsoft Office, Google products, photography, and more.

If you're fixated on a degree and completely miss my 26 years of real world experience, then you really don't get it and this won't work.